Guide to the Cass Gilbert Papers and Architectural Drawings 1883-1952 (Bulk 1900-1934) PR 21
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Project Files
  - Subseries I: Foldered Material
    - Shattuck School (Faribault, MN) (Box 2 of 2), 1901-1922 (Offsite-box 324)
    - Soldiers and Sailors Memorial (Duluth, MN) (Box 1 of 2), 1915-1924 (Offsite-box 324)
    - Soldiers and Sailors Memorial (Duluth, MN) (Box 2 of 2), 1915-1924 (Offsite-box 325)
    - Spaulding Building (Portland, OR) (Box 1 of 4), 1903-1923 (Offsite-box 325)
    - Spaulding Building (Portland, OR) (Box 2 of 4), 1903-1923 (Offsite-box 326)
    - Spaulding Building (Portland, OR) (Box 3 of 4), 1903-1923 (Offsite-box 327)
    - Spaulding Building (Portland, OR) (Box 4 of 4), 1903-1923 (Offsite-box 328)
    - Spaulding Property (Oakland, CA), 1901 (Offsite-box 328)
    - State Savings Bank (Butte, MT), 1906-1909 (Offsite-box 328)
    - Stone, Carpenter & Wilson, 1903-1904 (Offsite-box 329)
    - Strong, Sturgis & Company, 1901-1902 (Offsite-box 329)
    - Suffolk Savings Bank (Boston, MA) (Box 1 of 6), 1903-1909 (Offsite-box 329)
    - Suffolk Savings Bank (Boston, MA) (Box 2 of 6), 1903-1909 (Offsite-box 330)
    - Suffolk Savings Bank (Boston, MA) (Box 3 of 6), 1903-1909 (Offsite-box 331)
    - Suffolk Savings Bank (Boston, MA) (Box 4 of 6), 1903-1909 (Offsite-box 332)
    - Suffolk Savings Bank (Boston, MA) (Box 5 of 6), 1903-1909 (Offsite-box 333)
    - Suffolk Savings Bank (Boston, MA) (Box 6 of 6), 1903-1909 (Offsite-box 334)
    - Samuel Thomas Tomb (Tarrytown, NY), 1903-1907 (Offsite-box 335)
    - Samuel Thomas, Property, 1902-1903 (Offsite-box 335)
    - Thompson-Starrett Company, 1901-1904 (Offsite-box 335)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 1 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 335)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 2 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 336)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 3 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 337)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 4 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 338)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 5 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 339)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 6 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 340)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 7 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 341)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 8 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 342)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 9 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 343)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 10 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 344)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 11 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 345)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 12 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 346)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 13 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 347)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 14 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 348)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 15 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 349)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 16 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 350)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 17 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 351)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 18 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 352)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 19 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 353)
    - Union Central Life Insurance Building (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 20 of 20), 1906-1925 (Offsite-box 354)
    - Union Club (New York, NY) (Box 1 of 17), 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 354)
    - Union Club (New York, NY) (Box 2 of 17), 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 355)
    - Union Club (New York, NY) (Box 3 of 17), 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 356)
    - Union Club (New York, NY) (Box 4 of 17), 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 357)
    - Union Club (New York, NY) (Box 5 of 17), 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 358)
    - Union Club (New York, NY) (Box 6 of 17), 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 359)
    - Union Club (New York, NY) (Box 7 of 17), 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 360)
    - Union Club (New York, NY) (Box 8 of 17), 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 361)
    - Union Club (New York, NY) (Box 9 of 17), 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 362)
    - Union Club (New York, NY) (Box 10 of 17), 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 363)
    - Union Club (New York, NY) (Box 11 of 17), 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 364)
    - Union Club (New York, NY) (Box 12 of 17), 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 365)
    - Union Club (New York, NY) (Box 13 of 17), 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 366)
    - Union Club (New York, NY) (Box 14 of 17), 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 367)
    - Union Club (New York, NY) (Box 15 of 17), 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 368)
    - Union Club (New York, NY) (Box 16 of 17), 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 369)
    - Union Club (New York, NY) (Box 17 of 17), 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 370)
    - Union Engineering Building (St. Paul, MN), 1903 (Offsite-box 370)
    - Union Theological Seminary (New York, NY), 1906 (Offsite-box 370)
    - United Congregational Church (Bridgeport, CT) (Box 1 of 2), 1916-1924 (Offsite-box 370)
    - United Congregational Church (Bridgeport, CT) (Box 2 of 2), 1916-1924 (Offsite-box 371)
    - United States Army Supply Base (Brooklyn, New York) (Box 1 of 10), 1918-1932 (Offsite-box 371)
    - United States Army Supply Base (Brooklyn, New York) (Box 2 of 10), 1918-1932 (Offsite-box 372)
    - United States Army Supply Base (Brooklyn, New York) (Box 3 of 10), 1918-1932 (Offsite-box 373)
    - United States Army Supply Base (Brooklyn, New York) (Box 4 of 10), 1918-1932 (Offsite-box 374)
    - United States Army Supply Base (Brooklyn, New York) (Box 5 of 10), 1918-1932 (Offsite-box 375)
    - United States Army Supply Base (Brooklyn, New York) (Box 6 of 10), 1918-1932 (Offsite-box 376)
    - United States Army Supply Base (Brooklyn, New York) (Box 7 of 10), 1918-1932 (Offsite-box 377)
    - United States Army Supply Base (Brooklyn, New York) (Box 8 of 10), 1918-1932 (Offsite-box 378)
    - United States Army Supply Base (Brooklyn, New York) (Box 9 of 10), 1918-1932 (Offsite-box 379)
    - United States Army Supply Base (Brooklyn, New York) (Box 10 of 10), 1918-1932 (Offsite-box 380)
    - United States Chamber of Commerce (Washington, DC) (Box 1 of 12), 1919-1933 (Offsite-box 381)
    - United States Chamber of Commerce (Washington, DC) (Box 2 of 12), 1919-1933 (Offsite-box 382)
    - United States Chamber of Commerce (Washington, DC) (Box 3 of 12), 1919-1933 (Offsite-box 383)
    - United States Chamber of Commerce (Washington, DC) (Box 4 of 12), 1919-1933 (Offsite-box 384)
    - United States Chamber of Commerce (Washington, DC) (Box 5 of 12), 1919-1933 (Offsite-box 385)
    - United States Chamber of Commerce (Washington, DC) (Box 6 of 12), 1919-1933 (Offsite-box 386)
    - United States Chamber of Commerce (Washington, DC) (Box 7 of 12), 1919-1933 (Offsite-box 387)
    - United States Chamber of Commerce (Washington, DC) (Box 8 of 12), 1919-1933 (Offsite-box 388)
    - United States Chamber of Commerce (Washington, DC) (Box 9 of 12), 1919-1933 (Offsite-box 389)
    - United States Chamber of Commerce (Washington, DC) (Box 10 of 12), 1919-1933 (Offsite-box 390)
    - United States Chamber of Commerce (Washington, DC) (Box 11 of 12), 1919-1933 (Offsite-box 391)
    - United States Chamber of Commerce (Washington, DC) (Box 12 of 12), 1919-1933 (Offsite-box 392)
    - United States Court House (New York, NY) (Box 1 of 11), 1930-1935 (Offsite-box 393)
    - United States Court House (New York, NY) (Box 2 of 11), 1930-1935 (Offsite-box 394)
    - United States Court House (New York, NY) (Box 3 of 11), 1930-1935 (Offsite-box 395)
    - United States Court House (New York, NY) (Box 4 of 11), 1930-1935 (Offsite-box 396)
    - United States Court House (New York, NY) (Box 5 of 11), 1930-1935 (Offsite-box 397)
    - United States Court House (New York, NY) (Box 6 of 11), 1930-1935 (Offsite-box 398)
    - United States Court House (New York, NY) (Box 7 of 11), 1930-1935 (Offsite-box 399)
    - United States Court House (New York, NY) (Box 8 of 11), 1930-1935 (Offsite-box 400)
    - United States Court House (New York, NY) (Box 9 of 11), 1930-1935 (Offsite-box 401)
    - United States Court House (New York, NY) (Box 10 of 11), 1930-1935 (Offsite-box 402)
    - United States Court House (New York, NY) (Box 11 of 11), 1930-1935 (Offsite-box 403)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 1 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 404)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 2 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 405)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 3 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 406)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 4 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 407)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 5 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 408)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 6 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 409)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 7 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 410)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 8 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 411)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 9 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 412)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 10 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 413)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 11 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 414)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 12 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 415)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 13 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 416)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 14 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 417)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 15 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 418)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 16 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 419)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 17 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 420)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 18 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 421)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 19 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 422)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 20 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 423)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 21 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 424)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 22 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 425)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 23 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 426)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 24 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 427)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 25 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 428)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 26 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 429)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 27 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 430)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 28 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 431)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 29 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 432)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 30 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 433)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 31 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 434)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 32 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 435)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 33 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 436)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 34 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 437)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 35 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 438)
    - United States Custom House (New York, NY) (Box 36 of 36), 1899-1934 (Offsite-box 439)
    - United States Department of Agriculture (Washington, DC), 1901-1905 (Offsite-box 439)
    - United States Legation Building (Ottawa, Canada) (Box 1 of 4), 1928-1934 (Offsite-box 439)
    - United States Legation Building (Ottawa, Canada) (Box 2 of 4), 1928-1934 (Offsite-box 440)
    - United States Legation Building (Ottawa, Canada) (Box 3 of 4), 1928-1934 (Offsite-box 441)
    - United States Legation Building (Ottawa, Canada) (Box 4 of 4), 1928-1934 (Offsite-box 442)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 1 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 442)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 2 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 443)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 3 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 444)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 4 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 445)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 5 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 446)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 6 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 447)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 7 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 448)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 8 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 449)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 9 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 450)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 10 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 451)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 11 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 452)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 12 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 453)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 13 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 454)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 14 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 455)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 15 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 456)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 16 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 457)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 17 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 458)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 18 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 459)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 19 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 460)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 20 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 461)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 21 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 462)
    - United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D.C.) (Box 22 of 22), 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 463)
    - United States Treasury Department Annex (Washington, D.C.) (Box 1 of 5), 1917-1931 (Offsite-box 463)
    - United States Treasury Department Annex (Washington, D.C.) (Box 2 of 5), 1917-1931 (Offsite-box 464)
    - United States Treasury Department Annex (Washington, D.C.) (Box 3 of 5), 1917-1931 (Offsite-box 465)
    - United States Treasury Department Annex (Washington, D.C.) (Box 4 of 5), 1917-1931 (Offsite-box 466)
    - United States Treasury Department Annex (Washington, D.C.) (Box 5 of 5), 1917-1931 (Offsite-box 467)
    - University of Minnesota (Minneapolis, MN) (Box 1 of 2), 1906-1931 (Offsite-box 467)
    - University of Minnesota (Minneapolis, MN) (Box 2 of 2), 1906-1931 (Offsite-box 468)
    - University of Texas (Austin, TX) (Box 1 of 13), 1909-1927 (Offsite-box 469)
    - University of Texas (Austin, TX) (Box 2 of 13), 1909-1927 (Offsite-box 470)
    - University of Texas (Austin, TX) (Box 3 of 13), 1909-1927 (Offsite-box 471)
    - University of Texas (Austin, TX) (Box 4 of 13), 1909-1927 (Offsite-box 472)
    - University of Texas (Austin, TX) (Box 5 of 13), 1909-1927 (Offsite-box 473)
    - University of Texas (Austin, TX) (Box 6 of 13), 1909-1927 (Offsite-box 474)
    - University of Texas (Austin, TX) (Box 7 of 13), 1909-1927 (Offsite-box 475)
    - University of Texas (Austin, TX) (Box 8 of 13), 1909-1927 (Offsite-box 476)
    - University of Texas (Austin, TX) (Box 9 of 13), 1909-1927 (Offsite-box 477)
    - University of Texas (Austin, TX) (Box 10 of 13), 1909-1927 (Offsite-box 478)
    - University of Texas (Austin, TX) (Box 11 of 13), 1909-1927 (Offsite-box 479)
    - University of Texas (Austin, TX) (Box 12 of 13), 1909-1927 (Offsite-box 480)
    - University of Texas (Austin, TX) (Box 13 of 13), 1909-1927 (Offsite-box 481)
    - Vicksburg Monument (Vicksburg, MN), 1904-1906 (Offsite-box 481)
    - Ward Tomb (Newark, NJ), 1905-1913 (Offsite-box 482)
    - Ware, James E. & Sons, 1904 (Offsite-box 482)
    - Warehouse Cold Storage Project (St. Paul, MN), 1901-1904 (Offsite-box 482)
    - Warehouse Project (St. Paul, MN), 1902 (Offsite-box 482)
    - Washington DC Mall Preservation (Washington, DC), 1903-1904 (Offsite-box 482)
    - Washington State Capitol (Olympia, WA), 1893 (Offsite-box 482)
    - Waterbury Club (Waterbury, CT) (Box 1 of 4), 1914-1925 (Offsite-box 482)
    - Waterbury Club (Waterbury, CT) (Box 2 of 4), 1914-1925 (Offsite-box 483)
    - Waterbury Club (Waterbury, CT) (Box 3 of 4), 1914-1925 (Offsite-box 484)
    - Waterbury Club (Waterbury, CT) (Box 4 of 4), 1914-1925 (Offsite-box 485)
    - Waterbury Municipal Building (Waterbury, CT) (Box 1 of 10), 1913-1920 (Offsite-box 485)
    - Waterbury Municipal Building (Waterbury, CT) (Box 2 of 10), 1913-1920 (Offsite-box 486)
    - Waterbury Municipal Building (Waterbury, CT) (Box 3 of 10), 1913-1920 (Offsite-box 487)
    - Waterbury Municipal Building (Waterbury, CT) (Box 4 of 10), 1913-1920 (Offsite-box 488)
    - Waterbury Municipal Building (Waterbury, CT) (Box 5 of 10), 1913-1920 (Offsite-box 489)
    - Waterbury Municipal Building (Waterbury, CT) (Box 6 of 10), 1913-1920 (Offsite-box 490)
    - Waterbury Municipal Building (Waterbury, CT) (Box 7 of 10), 1913-1920 (Offsite-box 491)
    - Waterbury Municipal Building (Waterbury, CT) (Box 8 of 10), 1913-1920 (Offsite-box 492)
    - Waterbury Municipal Building (Waterbury, CT) (Box 9 of 10), 1913-1920 (Offsite-box 493)
    - Waterbury Municipal Building (Waterbury, CT) (Box 10 of 10), 1913-1920 (Offsite-box 494)
    - Waterbury National Bank (Waterbury, CT) (Box 1 of 6), 1918-1926 (Offsite-box 494)
    - Waterbury National Bank (Waterbury, CT) (Box 2 of 6), 1918-1926 (Offsite-box 495)
    - Waterbury National Bank (Waterbury, CT) (Box 3 of 6), 1918-1926 (Offsite-box 496)
    - Waterbury National Bank (Waterbury, CT) (Box 4 of 6), 1918-1926 (Offsite-box 497)
    - Waterbury National Bank (Waterbury, CT) (Box 5 of 6), 1918-1926 (Offsite-box 498)
    - Waterbury National Bank (Waterbury, CT) (Box 6 of 6), 1918-1926 (Offsite-box 499)
    - Waterproofing Companies, 1901 (Offsite-box 499)
    - West Point Project (West Point, NY), 1903 (Offsite-box 499)
    - West Street Building (New York, NY) (Box 1 of 4), 1905-1933 (Offsite-box 499)
    - West Street Building (New York, NY) (Box 2 of 4), 1905-1933 (Offsite-box 500)
    - West Street Building (New York, NY) (Box 3 of 4), 1905-1933 (Offsite-box 501)
    - West Street Building (New York, NY) (Box 4 of 4), 1905-1933 (Offsite-box 502)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 1 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 503)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 2 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 504)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 3 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 505)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 4 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 506)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 5 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 507)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 6 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 508)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 7 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 509)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 8 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 510)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 9 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 511)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 10 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 512)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 11 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 513)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 12 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 514)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 13 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 515)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 14 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 516)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 15 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 517)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 16 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 518)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 17 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 519)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 18 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 520)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 19 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 521)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 20 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 522)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 21 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 523)
    - West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, WV) (Box 22 of 22), 1921-1952 (Offsite-box 524)
    - Western Press Clippings Bureau, 1901, 1905 (Offsite-box 524)
    - Williams Warehouse (New York, NY) (Box 1 of 3), 1927-1930 (Offsite-box 524)
    - Williams Warehouse (New York, NY) (Box 2 of 3), 1927-1930 (Offsite-box 525)
    - Williams Warehouse (New York, NY) (Box 3 of 3), 1927-1930 (Offsite-box 526)
    - Wisconsin State Capitol (Madison, WI) (Box 1 of 2), 1903-1907 (Offsite-box 526)
    - Wisconsin State Capitol (Madison, WI) (Box 2 of 2), 1903-1907 (Offsite-box 527)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 1 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 528)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 2 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 529)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 3 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 530)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 4 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 531)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 5 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 532)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 6 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 533)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 7 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 534)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 8 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 535)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 9 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 536)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 10 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 537)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 11 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 538)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 12 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 539)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 13 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 540)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 14 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 541)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 15 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 542)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 16 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 543)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 17 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 544)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 18 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 545)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 19 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 546)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 20 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 547)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 21 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 548)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 22 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 549)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 23 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 550)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 24 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 551)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 25 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 552)
    - Woolworth Building (New York, NY) (Box 26 of 39), 1910-1933 (Offsite-box 553)